

Jusa Leander

Fullstack developer

Telephone 040 733 5059

jusaleander@hotmail.com

Profile

26 years old guy who has been developement for a year now. Previous experience from soundand mechanical engineering. Visit my website for a better view of my skills and project portfolio!

On free time I produce and play program a lot. I live in Helsinki with my girlfriend and our little

Language Skills

Finnish	•	•	•	•	•
English	•	•	•	•	•
Swedish	•	•	•	•	•
Russian	•	•	•	•	•

Experience

Fullstack developer studies

2018 - Present

- Spring semester HTML, CSS, JS
- Autumn semester Node.js, React, MySql
- Independent projects

Construction worker, Barona

2017

- Various tasks on both big and small sites
- Team leading, safety managing, cleaning, logistics

Security, G4S

2014

High level security in data center worksite

Live Sound Engineer, Teekkareiden Musiikkikerho ry

2011 - 2015

- Setting up and managing live gigs
- Live mixing in various venues
- Responsibilities in organization

Education

Lappeenranta University of Technology

2011 - 2017

Mechanical engineering, International Business

Haminan Lukio

2011

Ylioppilas 2011

Programming Skills

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Node.js

MySQL